Guide to the Cannery Workers and Farm Laborers Union Local 7 Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- CANNERY WORKERS' AND FARM LABORERS' UNION, LOCAL 18257 (American Federation of Labor), 1933-1937, RECORD GROUP 2 (Box-folder 7/1-9/22)
  - General Files, 1933-1953; Subgroup A (Box-folder 7/1-9/17)
    - SUBJECT SERIES, 1934-1937; SERIES VII (Box-folder 8/7-8/13)
      - Resignations, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 8/11)
      - Statistics, 1934-1937 (Box-folder 8/12)
      - Yakima Filipinos, 1937, Undated (Box-folder 8/13)
    - NEGOTIATIONS, CONTRACTS, AGREEMENTS, 1934-1937; SERIES VIII (Box-folder 8/14-8/15)
    - CASE FILES, 1934-1937; SERIES IX (Box-folder 8/16-8/23)
      - Arce, Domingo, 1937 (Box-folder 8/16)
      - Balagot, Sammy, 1934 (Box-folder 8/17)
      - Claims--Snug Harbor, 1937 (Box-folder 8/18)
      - Santos, Cuadra vs Pacific American Fisheries, 1936 (Box-folder 8/19)
      - Torres, Vincent--Deceased, 1936 (Box-folder 8/20)
      - Vitter and Stephenson, 1937 (Box-folder 8/21)
      - Files Closed in 1937 (Box-folder 8/22)
      - Miscellaneous, 1934 (Box-folder 8/23)
    - COURT PAPERS, 1937; SERIES X (Box-folder 8/24-9/1)
      - AFL vs CWFLU Local 18257, 1937 (Box-folder 8/24)
      - CWFLU Local 18257 vs AFL, 1937 (Box-folder 8/25)
      - Fernandez vs Tanagi, 1934 (Box-folder 8/26)
      - La Bonite vs CWFLU 18257, 1937 (Box-folder 8/27)
      - Quilantang vs Conrad Espe, et al, 1937 (Box-folder 9/1)
    - CONFERENCES, 1933-1935; SERIES XI (Box-folder 9/4)
    - RESOLUTIONS, 1936-1937; SERIES XII (Box-folder 9/5)
    - AFFADAVITS, 1933-1937; SERIES XIII (Box-folder 9/6)
    - PETITIONS, 1933, 1936-1937; SERIES XIV (Box-folder 9/7)
    - ALASKA SALMON INDUSTRY, Undated; SERIES XV (Box-folder 9/8)
    - SETTLEMENT STATEMENT, 1937; SERIES XVI (Box-folder 9/9)
    - LISTS, 1934-1939; 1952-1953; SERIES XVII (Box-folder 9/10-9/14)
      - Companies, 1937, Undated (Box-folder 9/10)
      - Delegates, 1937 (Box-folder 9/11)
      - Executive Board meetings attendance (bd. vol.), 1934, 1936-1939, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 9/12)
      - Membership, 1935-1937, Undated (Box-folder 9/13)
      - Miscellaneous, 1937, Undated (Box-folder 9/14)
    - SPEECHES AND WRITINGS, 1934, Undated; SERIES XVIII (Box-folder 9/15)
    - NOTES, Undated; SERIES XIX (Box-folder 9/16)
    - EPHEMERA, 1928-1936, Undated; SERIES XX (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Continuation Committee, 1937; Subgroup B (Box-folder 9/18)
  - Election Committee, 1937; Subgroup C (Box-folder 9/19)
  - Grievance Committee, 1936-1937; Subgroup D (Box-folder 9/20)
  - Policy Committee, 1937; Subgroup E (Box-folder 9/21)
  - Northwest Council of Cannery Workers, 1937; Subgroup F (Box-folder 9/22)
- CANNERY WORKERS AND FARM LABORERS' UNION, LOCAL 7 (UNITED CANNERY, AGRICULTURAL, PACKING & ALLIED WORKERS OF AMERICA-CIO), 1933-1952; 1981-1982; RECORD GROUP 3 (Box-folder 10/1-23/28)
  This record group consists of meeting minutes, agendas, reports, memoranda and correspondence that give insight into the day-to-day workings of local union and labor coalitions, as well as the relationship bet ween local unions and their national-level counterparts. Additionally, this record group includes the brochures, handouts, reports, agendas and meeting minutes relating to special union events, such as conventions, summits, strikes, banquets and fundraisers.
  Within each record group, a filing system was devised for the union's correspondence. First, a division was made between correspondence within the union and external correspondence. Internal correspondence was divided between members correspondence (usually separate in the original order), correspondence among officers, correspondence with branches, delegates and the parent international. Member's correspondence is arranged by year, all other correspondence is arranged alphabetically The outgoing letters series consists of flyers and other mailings sent mainly to members.
  - General Records, 1936-1944; Subgroup A (Box-folder 10/1-21/34)
    - ORGANIZATIONAL FEATURES, 1933; SERIES I (Box-folder 10/1-4)
    - OUTGOING LETTERS, 1937-1944; SERIES II (Box-folder 10/5-10/17)
      - General, 1937-1944 (Box-folder 10/5-6)
      - Notices to members, announcements, etc., 1937-1944 (Box-folder 10/7-8)
      - Letters of recommendation, 1937-1944 (Box-folder 10/9-15)
      - Re: Release from employers, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 10/16-17)
    - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE--UCAPAWA, 1938-1944; SERIES III (Box-folder 10/18-10/28)
      - International General Secretary-Treasurer, 1938-1944 (Box-folder 10/18-19)
      - Dellama, Rose, International Reps., 1944 (Box-folder 10/20)
      - Espe, Conrad, International V.P. & Executive V.P., 1938-1944 (Box-folder 10/21)
      - Henderson, Donald, International President, 1938-1944 (Box-folder 10/22-25)
      - Tiller, Dixie, International V.P. & Regional Director, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 10/26)
      - Other Officers, 1939-1945 (Box-folder 10/27)
      - District 1, 1938-1941 (Box-folder 10/28)
    - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE--Locals & Branches, 1937-1945; SERIES IV (Box-folder 10/29-10/52)
      - Local 5--San Francisco, 1938-1943 (Box-folder 10/29-36)
      - Local 7--Portland Branch, 1937 (Box-folder 10/37)
      - Local 7--San Francisco Branch, 1943-1945 (Box-folder 10/38-40)
      - Local 20--Stockton, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 10/41)
      - Local 222--Petersburg, Alaska, 1937-1939 (Box-folder 10/42-43)
      - Local 226--Portland, 1938-1945 (Box-folder 10/44-46)
      - Local 7 Portland Branch, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 10/47)
      - Local 7 Stockton Branch, 1944 (Box-folder 10/48)
      - Local 236--Hoonah, Alaska, 1944 (Box-folder 10/49)
      - Local 237--Ketchikan, Alaska, 1937-1944 (Box-folder 10/50-51)
      - Other UCAPAWA Locals, 1938-1941 (Box-folder 10/52)
    - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE--Other Unions, 1937-1944; SERIES V (Box-folder 10/53-11/6)
      - A-D, 1939-1944 (Box-folder 10/53)
      - F, 1938-1944 (Box-folder 10/54)
      - H-L, 1938-1942 (Box-folder 11/1)
      - I.L.W.U. (Locals & international), 1938-1941 (Box-folder 11/2)
      - M-N, 1938-1944 (Box-folder 11/3)
      - Newspaper Guild, American. Local 82 (Seattle), 1937-1944 (Box-folder 11/4)
      - O-W, 1938-1943 (Box-folder 11/5)
      - Workers Alliance of America (and Locals), 1938-1940 (Box-folder 11/6)
    - INTERNAL CORRESPONDENCE--Officers & Executive Council, 1937-1945; SERIES VI (Box-folder 11/7-11/16)
      - Executive Board, 1938-1944 (Box-folder 11/7)
      - Executive Council, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 11/8)
      - Cabatit, Irineo R., 1937-1939, 1943 (Box-folder 11/9-10)
      - Rojo, Trinidad A., 1939-1944 (Box-folder 11/11-12)
      - Treasurer (M.S. Ventura & Johnny Lucero), 1942-1943 (Box-folder 11/13-14)
      - Fox, Ernest (Alaska organizer), 1938 (Box-folder 11/15)
      - Miscellaneous, 1937-1945 (Box-folder 11/16)
    - PERSONAL CORRESPONDENCE--Officers, 1938-1944; SERIES VII (Box-folder 11/17-11/18)
      - Mori, Prudencio P., 1939, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 11/17)
      - Ventura, Mamerto S., 1938, 1941, 1943 (Box-folder 11/18)
    - INTERNAL CORRESPONDENCE--Delegates & Organizers, 1938-1944; SERIES VIII (Box-folder 11/19-11/35)
      - Alaska Pacific Salmon Co., Excursion Inlet, Kate, Port Althorp, Rose Inlet, Sand Point, Sunny Point, Ketchikan, 1938-1940, 1943 (Box-folder 11/19-20)
      - Red Salmon Packing Co., Hawk Inlet, Narnek, Egigik, Carmel, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 11/21)
      - P.E. Harris Co., False Pass, Hawk Inlet, 1938-1940, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 11/22)
      - InterCoastal Packing Co., S.S. Ogantz, 1939 (Box-folder 11/23)
      - Kadiak Fisheries, Port Bailey, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 11/24)
      - Libby, McNeill & Libby, Yakutat, Libbyville, Kenai, Koggeoung, Taku Harbor, Craig, George Inlet, 1938-1940, 1943 (Box-folder 11/25-26)
      - Nakat Packing Co., Waterfall, Union Bay, Hidden Inlet, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 11/27)
      - New England Fish Co., Cordova, Ketchikan, Noyes Island, 1938-1939, 1944 (Box-folder 11/28)
      - Pacific American Fisheries, Nornek, Shumigan, Alitak, Squaw Harbor, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 11/29)
      - San Juan Fishing & Packing Co., Port San Juan, Uganik Bay, Sawmill Bay, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 11/30)
      - Delegates--Miscellaneous, 1938-1939, 1943 (Box-folder 11/31)
      - Delegates--Telegrams, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 11/32-33)
      - Delegates--Reports from canneries, 1944 (Box-folder 11/34-35)
    - INTERNAL CORRESPONDENCE--Members, 1937-1945; SERIES IX (Box-folder 11/36-12/25)
    - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE--Membership Inquiries, 1938-1946; SERIES X (Box-folder 12/26-12/33)
    - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE--Regarding:, 1938-1944; SERIES XI (Box-folder 12/34-12/37)
      - Advertising and publicity, 1944 (Box-folder 12/34)
      - American Ramie Company, 1938 (Box-folder 12/35)
      - Leaves of Absence, 1938-1940 (Box-folder 12/36)
      - 4 days picket Deductions--Sunnypoint--Beagle Packaging Company, 1939 (Box-folder 12/37)
    - GENERAL CORRESPONDENCE--External, 1937-1944; SERIES XII (Box-folder 13/1-14/29)
      - Alaska. Territory of 1940 (Box-folder 13/1)
      - Alaska. Unemployment Compensation Commission, 1940-1943 (Box-folder 13/2)
      - Alaska Pacific Salmon Company, 1937-1940 (Box-folder 13/3)
      - Alaska Packers Association, 1944 (Box-folder 13/4)
      - Alaska Salmon Industry, 1939-1945 (Box-folder 13/5-13/10)
      - Alaska Travel Control Bureau, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 13/11)
      - American Committee for Protection of Foreign Born, 1938-1941 (Box-folder 13/12)
      - Anderson, George--Attorney, 1938-1944 (Box-folder 13/13)
      - Arcade Building and Realty Company, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 13/14)
      - Astoria & Puget Sound Canning Company, 1937-1944 (Box-folder 13/15)
      - Miscellaneous A, 1937-1945 (Box-folder 13/16)
      - Harry Bridges Defense Committee, 1939-1941 (Box-folder 13/17)
      - Henry Broderick, Inc., 1940-1942 (Box-folder 13/18)
      - Buildings Trade Council, Seattle, 1944 (Box-folder 13/19)
      - Miscellaneous B, 1937-1944 (Box-folder 13/20)
      - Canadian Bank of Commerce, 1938-1944 (Box-folder 13/21)
      - Canned Salmon Industry, 1938-1940 (Box-folder 13/22)
      - Central Labor Council, Juneau, 1936-1938 (Box-folder 13/23)
      - Central Labor Council, Seattle, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 13/24)
      - C.I.O. California Research Director, 1944 (Box-folder 13/25)
      - C.I.O., 1938-1947 (Box-folder 13/25a)
      - C.I.O. Northwest Region, 1937-1947 (Box-folder 13/25b)
      - Committee for the Celebration of the President's Birthday, 1939 (Box-folder 13/26)
      - Copper River Packing Co., 1937-1944 (Box-folder 13/27)
      - Miscellaneous C, 1937-1944 (Box-folder 13/28)
      - De Lacy, Hugh, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 13/29)
      - Miscellaneous D, 1937-1944 (Box-folder 13/30)
      - Miscellaneous E, 1938 (Box-folder 13/31)
      - Farwest Fisherman, Inc., 1939 (Box-folder 13/32)
      - Federated Fishermens Council of the Pacific Coast, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 13/33)
      - Fidalgo Island Packing Company, 1944 (Box-folder 13/34)
      - Filipino-American Citizenship Council, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 13/35)
      - Four Stores Garage, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 13/36)
      - Miscellaneous F, 1938-1944 (Box-folder 13/37)
      - Gershon, Perry R.--Attorney, 1940-1945 (Box-folder 13/38)
      - W.R. Gilbert Packing Co., 1942 (Box-folder 3/39)
      - Goodrich, W.F., 1940 (Box-folder 13/40)
      - Miscellaneous G, 1937-1939 (Box-folder 13/41)
      - G.P. Halferty and Company, 1944 (Box-folder 13/42)
      - P.E. Harris and Company, 1937-1944 (Box-folder 13/43)
      - Hood Bay Salmon Company, 1944 (Box-folder 13/44)
      - Miscellaneous H, 1937-1942 (Box-folder 13/45)
      - Institute of International Relations, 1944 (Box-folder 13/46)
      - International Labor Defense, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 13/47)
      - International Workers Order, 1938 (Box-folder 13/48)
      - Miscellaneous I, 1937-1940 (Box-folder 13/49)
      - Japanese Growers Association, 1938 (Box-folder 13/50)
      - Joint Anti-Fascist Refugee Committee, 1944 (Box-folder 13/51)
      - Miscellaneous J, 1944 (Box-folder 13/52)
      - King County Welfare Department, 1938 (Box-folder 13/53)
      - King-Ramsay-Conner Defense Committee, 1940 (Box-folder 13/54)
      - Kingston, Ross--Attorney, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 13/55)
      - Kirk Manufacturing Co., 1940 (Box-folder 13/56)
      - Miscellaneous K, 1937-1944 (Box-folder 13/57)
      - Labor Committee on the Oklahoma Criminal Syndicalism Case, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 13/58)
      - Labor Consumers League, 1944 (Box-folder 13/59)
      - Labor Unions Relief Council, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 13/60)
      - Labors Non-Partisan League, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 13/61)
      - Lauckhart, W.J., 1939-1944 (Box-folder 13/62)
      - Libby, McNeill & Libby Co., 1938-1944 (Box-folder 13/63)
      - Lutheran Compass Mission, 1944 (Box-folder 13/64)
      - Miscellaneous L, 1937-1943 (Box-folder 13/65)
      - Metzger-Parker Co., 1944 (Box-folder 13/66)
      - Vincent D. Miller, Inc., 1943-1944 (Box-folder 13/67)
      - Molthan, James J.--Attorney, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 13/68)
      - Miscellaneous M, 1938-1941 (Box-folder 13/69)
      - Nakat Packing Co., 1937-1944 (Box-folder 13/70)
      - National Labor Bureau, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 13/71)
      - National Maritime Union of America, 1939-1944 (Box-folder 13/72)
      - New England Fish Co., 1937-1944 (Box-folder 13/73)
      - Newspapers, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 13/74)
      - Miscellaneous N, 1939-1944 (Box-folder 13/75)
      - Miscellaneous O, 1938 (Box-folder 13/76)
      - Pacific American Fisheries, Inc., 1937-1944 (Box-folder 13/77)
      - Pacific Fishermen, 1940-1944 (Box-folder 13/79)
      - Pacific Telephone & Telegraph Co., 1939-1944 (Box-folder 13/80)
      - Peoples National Bank of Washington, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 13/81)
      - Philippines, Resident Commissioner, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 13/82-84)
      - Pioneer Seafoods Co., 1937-1944 (Box-folder 13/85)
      - Postal Telegraph--Cable Co., 1939-1941 (Box-folder 13/86)
      - Prentice--Hall Inc., 1938-1940 (Box-folder 13/87)
      - Prince William Sound Fishermen's Union, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 13/88)
      - Miscellaneous P, 1937-1944 (Box-folder 13/89)
      - Red Salmon Canning Co., 1938-1944 (Box-folder 13/90)
      - Franklin D. Roosevelt Library, Inc., 1939 (Box-folder 13/91)
      - Miscellaneous R, 1938 (Box-folder 13/92)
      - Seattle. City of, 1938-1944 (Box-folder 13/93)
      - Seattle Post-Intelligencer, 1939-1942 (Box-folder 13/94)
      - Sebastian--Stuart Fish Co., 1937-1944 (Box-folder 13/95)
      - Miscellaneous S, 1936-1944 (Box-folder 13/96)
      - Miscellaneous T, 1940-1944 (Box-folder 13/97)
      - Uganik Fisheries, Inc., 1937-1944 (Box-folder 13/98)
      - U.S. Army. First Filipino Infantry, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 13/99)
      - U.S. Congress and White House, 1937-1944 (Box-folder 13/100)
      - U.S. Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1938-1944 (Box-folder 13/101)
      - U.S. Federal Security Agency--Social Security Board, 1938-1944 (Box-folder 13/102)
      - U.S. Interior Dept., 1940-1944 (Box-folder 13/103)
      - U.S. Internal Revenue Service, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 13/104)
      - U.S. Justice Dept.--Prisons & Parole Boards, 1938-1944 (Box-folder 13/105)
      - U.S. Justice Dept.--Immigration & Naturalization, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 13/106)
      - U.S. Labor Dept., 1938-1944 (Box-folder 13/107)
      - U.S. Maritime Commission, 1940 (Box-folder 3/108)
      - U.S. National Labor Relations Board, 1938-1940, 1944 (Box-folder 4/1-4)
      - U.S. National War Labor Board, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 14/5)
      - U.S. Office of Price Administration--Rationing Boards, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 14/6)
      - U.S. Selective Service, 1941-1944 (Box-folder 14/7-12)
      - U.S. Selective Service--Deferment Applications, 1942 (Box-folder 14/13)
      - U.S. Selective Service--Notices of Classification, 1942 (Box-folder 14/14)
      - U.S. State Dept. Visa Division, 1944 (Box-folder 14/15)
      - U.S. War Dept., 1944 (Box-folder 14/16)
      - U.S. War Manpower Commission, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 14/17)
      - U.S.--Various Government Agencies, 1939-1945 (Box-folder 14/18)
      - Miscellaneous U, 1938-1940 (Box-folder 14/19)
      - Washington State (Various agencies), 1938-1943 (Box-folder 14/20)
      - Washington. University, 1939-1942 (Box-folder 14/21)
      - Washington Pension Union, 1940 (Box-folder 14/22)
      - Western Union Telegraph Co., 1939-1944 (Box-folder 14/23)
      - L.G. Wingard Packing Co., 1943-1944 (Box-folder 14/24)
      - Women's Committee for Peace, 1940 (Box-folder 14/25)
      - Miscellaneous W, 1937-1944 (Box-folder 14/26)
      - Miscellaneous Y-Z, 1938-1940 (Box-folder 14/27-28)
      - Unidentified, 1940 (Box-folder 14/29)
    - ADMINISTRATIVE MEMORANDA, 1944; SERIES XIII (Box-folder 14/30)
    - SUBJECT SERIES, 1936-1945; SERIES XIV (Box-folder 14/31-15/20)
      - 1 AFL-CIO Jurisdictional Dispute, 1938 (Box-folder 14/31)
      - Alaska Salmon Industry, Inc., 1943 (Box-folder 14/32)
      - Alaska Travel Control--for passes, 1943 (Box-folder 14/33)
      - Ayamo--AFL-SIU, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 14/34)
      - Bills--U.S. Congress, 1935-1940 (Box-folder 14/35)
      - Bills--Washington State Legislature, 1943 (Box-folder 14/36)
      - Bristol Bay Area Resident Workers, 1944 (Box-folder 14/37)
      - Building & Offices, 1940-1945 (Box-folder 14/38)
      - Burial Fund, 1937-1940 (Box-folder 14/39)
      - Supplements, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 15/9)
      - UCAPAWA Literature, 1940-1944 (Box-folder 15/10)
      - Unemployed and Registrations, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 15/11)
      - Unemployment, 1937-1940 (Box-folder 15/12)
      - Unemployment Compensation, 1940-1942 (Box-folder 15/13)
      - Union Dues Rates, 1941-1945 (Box-folder 15/14)
      - Union Hall, 1937-1939 (Box-folder 15/15)
      - Union Building & Offices, 1941 (Box-folder 15/16)
      - U.S. War Manpower Commission Retention of Experienced Cannery Workers, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 15/17)
      - War Bonds, 1942-1944 (Box-folder 15/18)
      - War Production Board, Undated (Box-folder 15/19)
      - Wagner Act--opinions, decisions, interpretation of 1936-1938 (Box-folder 15/20)
    - ELECTIONS, 1937-1945; SERIES XV (Box-folder 15/21-46)
    - NEGOTIATIONS, CONTRACTS AND AGREEMENTS, 1937-1946; SERIES XVI (Box-folder 15/47-16/23)
    - CASE FILES, 1936-1944; SERIES XVII (Box-folder 16/24-16/54)
      - C.A. Abella re: Alitak Foremen, 1944 (Box-folder 16/24)
      - A.P.A. Discrimination Case, 1943 (Box-folder 16/26)
      - Bautista and Sevilla (Craig Cannery), 1938 (Box-folder 16/27)
      - Irvin Bluestiens Case--Sunny Point, 1938 (Box-folder 16/28)
      - Cases Pending, 1938 (Box-folder 16/29)
      - Craig Case (Craig Packing Co.--formerly Lindenberger Co., 1942 (Box-folder 16/30)
      - Culinary Department--Ships Enroute--Bristol Bay, 1943 (Box-folder 16/31)
      - CWFLU #7 Investigation Committee, 1938 (Box-folder 16/32)
      - CWFLU #7 vs Glacier Seafood Company, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 16/33)
      - CWFLU #7 vs Pioneer Seafoods, 1938 (Box-folder 16/34)
      - Duyungan--Simon Memorial Fund, 1936-1939 (Box-folder 16/35-16/37)
      - Foremen--assignments, cases, complaints, etc., 1938 (Box-folder 16/38)
      - Ricardo S. Garo--burial costs, 1937 (Box-folder 16/39)
      - Owen Huskins and Raymund Johnson Case vs Pacific American Fisheries, 1938 (Box-folder 16/40)
      - List of complaints filed to NLRB by individuals, Undated (Box-folder 16/41)
      - 16/42 F. Mauli--burial fund 1939
      - Nellie Juan Case, 1942 (Box-folder 16/43)
      - Ted Niedo Case, 1943 (Box-folder 16/44)
      - NLRB--charges of unfair labor practices against Canned Salmon Inc., 1938 (Box-folder 16/45)
      - Petersburg Cannery, 1943 (Box-folder 16/46)
      - S.S. Quezon Case (losses), 1941 (Box-folder 16/47)
      - Tanguilig, Leo and Descargar, Rufino--deceased, 1939 (Box-folder 16/48)
      - Harry Thibedeau vs California Packing Company, 1937 (Box-folder 16/49)
      - Ponce Torres, 1937-1940 (Box-folder 16/50-16/53)
      - Baselizo G. Villalobos Case, 1944 (Box-folder 16/54)
    - COURT EXHIBITS--Local #7--San Francisco Branch, 1929-1944; SERIES XVIII (Box-folder 16/54)
    - COURT PAPERS, 1938-1940; SERIES XIX (Box-folder 16/56-16/63)
      - Margaret Buyungan vs CWFLU #18257/#7, 1939 (Box-folder 16/56)
      - CWFLU vs AFL, 1937 (Box-folder 16/57)
      - J.E. Evangelista vs CWFLU #7, 1939-1940 (Box-folder 16/58-60)
      - Kohler et. al. (CWFLU #7 members) vs Pacific American Fisheries, Inc., 1939 (Box-folder 16/61)
      - Labonite vs CWFLU #7, 1938 (Box-folder 16/62)
      - UCAPAWA vs Alaska Fish Cannery Workers of the Pacific (John Ayamo), 1940 (Box-folder 16/63)
    - HEARINGS--U.S. Labor Relations Board, 1941-1945; SERIES XX (Box-folder 17/1-17/9)
      - Miscellaneous, 1943-1944 (Box-folder 17/2-4)
      - Alaska Salmon Industry vs UCAPAWA #7, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 17/5-9)
    - TRIALS AND HEARINGS--Internal, 1938-1944; SERIES XXI (Box-folder 17/10-17/22)
      - Summons for Trials and Investigations, 1938-1940 (Box-folder 17/10)
      - Lucero vs Briones--Proceedings and Minutes of Executive Council, 1943 (Box-folder 17/11)
      - Lucero vs Briones--Exhibits, 1943 (Box-folder 7/12)
      - Rendon Hearing--Original Recording, 1944 (Box-folder 17/13)
      - Rendon Case--Proceedings and Minutes--Trial and Review, 1944 (Box-folder 17/14)
      - Navea Trial--Proceedings, 1944 (Box-folder 17/15-16)
      - Navea Case--Arguments at Trial, 1944 (Box-folder 17/17-18)
      - Navea Case--Exhibits, 1944 (Box-folder 17/19)
      - Proceedings of Navea Case--Trial and Summary, 1944 (Box-folder 17/20)
      - Trial of A. Bosconcillo and J. Monso, 1944 (Box-folder 17/21)
      - Trial of T. Reyes--incl. Board Meeting Minutes, 1939 (Box-folder 17/22)
    - PETITIONS, GRIEVANCES AND CLAIMS, 1937-1944; SERIES XXII (Box-folder 17/23-17/30)
    - RULES, 1937-1943; SERIES XXIII (Box-folder 17/31-17/38)
    - WRITINGS AND RESEARCH (T. Rojo), 1937-1945, Undated; SERIES XXIV (Box-folder 17/39-18/5)
    - NEWSLETTERS, 1937-1943; SERIES XXV (Box-folder 18/6-18/14)
      - Local 7, 1937-1943 (Box-folder 18/6-12)
      - Local 5, 1938-1942 (Box-folder 18/13)
      - Local 226, 1939 (Box-folder 18/14)
    - UCAPAWA, 1939-1944; SERIES XXVI (Box-folder 18/15-18/18)
      - Labor Relations Report, 1943-1945 (Box-folder 18/16)
      - Labor's Non-Partisan League, 1940 (Box-folder 18/17)
      - Others, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 18/18)
    - FOREMAN APPLICATIONS AND LISTS, 1937-1945; SERIES XXVII (Box-folder 18/19-18/22)
    - RESOLUTIONS, 1938-1940; SERIES XXVIII (Box-folder 18/23-18/28)
    - PETITIONS AND AFFIDAVITS, 1938-1940; SERIES IXXX (Box-folder 18/29-18/35)
    - NEWS RELEASES, 1937-1944; SERIES XXX (Box-folder 18/36-18/39)
    - REPORTS--Including Delegates, 1937-1944; SERIES XXXI (Box-folder 18/40-18/45)
    - CONFERENCES AND CONVENTIONS, 1937-1944; SERIES XXXII (Box-folder 18/46-18/56)
      - UCAPAWA National Convention, 1938, 1944 (Box-folder 18/46-47)
      - Federated Fishermens Council of the Pacific, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 18/48-50)
      - Alaska Cannery Foremen and Delegates, 1937 (Box-folder 18/51)
      - All Alaska Labor Convention, 1940, 1942 (Box-folder 18/52)
      - Cannery Workers Foremen's Conference, 1939 (Box-folder 18/53)
      - Public Power Conference, 1942 (Box-folder 18/54)
      - United Fishermen's Union of the Pacific, 1938 (Box-folder 18/55)
      - Miscellaneous, 1941 (Box-folder 18/56)
    - PROGRAMS, 1937-1942; SERIES XXXIII (Box-folder 19/1-19/2)
    - EPHEMERA, 1936-1944; SERIES XXXIV (Box-folder 19/3-19/7)
      - A.F.L. Leaflets, Undated (Box-folder 19/3)
      - Re: U.S. Government & Philippines, 1936-1942 (Box-folder 19/4)
      - Union Related, 1937-1945 (Box-folder 19/5)
      - Regarding World War II, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 19/6)
      - Miscellaneous, 1939-1944 (Box-folder 19/7)